Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vuongnguyen-89494b212 (LinkedIn) github.com/vuongng4716 (Personal)

Top Skills

Natural Language Processing (NLP)
Python (Programming Language)
Optical Character Recognition
(OCR)

Certifications

Data Engineering, Big Data, and Machine Learning on GCP

TensorFlow: Advanced Techniques

Microsoft Azure Machine Learning for Data Scientists

Advanced Machine Learning on Google Cloud Specialization

Create Machine Learning Models in Microsoft Azure

Vuong Nguyen

Al Engineer

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Summary

Experienced Artificial Intelligence Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Google Cloud Platform, Data Science, Github, Data Engineering, and TensorFlow. Strong engineering professional with a Engineer's degree focused in Mechatronics, Robotics, and Automation Engineering from Hanoi University of Science and Technology.

Experience

MB - Military Commercial Joint Stock Bank Al Engineer June 2022 - Present (2 years 10 months) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Evotek

Artificial Intelligence Developer April 2022 - Present (3 years) Vietnam

Ecorange
Al Engineer
June 2021 - April 2022 (11 months)

VHV Hitech Information Technology Technician March 2019 - February 2021 (2 years) Vietnam

Education

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Engineer's degree, Electronics, Robotics, and Automation Engineering · (September 2014 - February 2019)